# MARTINA COLOMBO

13/07/1994 04 59798893

jambokolo@gmail.com

# **Pastry Cook**

Passionate pastry cook with three years of experience. My goal is to improve my profession, learning new techniques and new ways to work and to obtain a position in a professional atmosphere that will present me with new ideas and good organizational skills, combined with my ability to work well under pressure.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

OCT. 2019 - FEB.2020

# NEW FARM DELI & CAFÈ, BRISBANE – AUSTRALIA

#### **PASTRY CHEF**

- Prepare all pastry items to specification of established recipes and to restaurant specification
- Create new pastry products according to restaurant and costumers requests
- Manage orders
- Responsible for mantaining clean work station

JULY 2019 - SEPT.2019

#### ACQUA E SALE RESTAURANT, ALBEROBELLO – ITALY

## **SEASONAL PASTRY COOK**

- Prepare all pastry items to specification of established recipes and to restaurant specification
- Work for a wedding with a pastry chef and his team preparing the sweet buffet

**OCT. 2018 – JUNE 2019** 

#### **FARINI MILAN - ITALY**

#### **HEAD PASTRY COOK**

- Create new cakes according to restaurant and costumers requests
- Solely responsible for mantaining clean work station
- Collaborate with charity organizations by producing cakes

**DEC. 2017 - SEPT 2018** 

#### ASOLA RESTAURANT, MILAN – ITALY

# **HEAD PASTRY COOK**

- Collaborate with the colleague to create new desserts, pastry and bread products
- Prepare all desserts of the menu
- Train new pastry apprentices
- Ensure all equipment was clean and in working condition
- Label and date all foods
- Manage orders
- Create desserts for monthly or weekly events such as business parties, fashion parties, etc

FEB. 2017 - DEC. 2017

## SIKELAIA RESTAURANT, MILAN – ITALY

# **PASTRY APPRENTICE**

- Maintain organization, cleanliness and sanitation in work areas and of equipment.
- Ensure station is prepared to meet anticipated level of business for the day.
- Assist in the development of new dessert and pastry products.

SEP. 2016 – JAN. 2017

#### **PECK MILAN - ITALY**

## **PASTRY APPRENTICE**

- Work harmoniously and professionally with co-workers and supervisors and actively participate in creating a positive teamwork environment
- Perform duties as assigned by culinary management
- Ensure station is prepared to meet anticipated level of business for the day
- Prepare a wide variety of goods such as cakes, cookies, gelato, etc. following traditional and modern recipes

## **EDUCATION**

**JUNE 2020** 

**CERITIFICATE: CHOCOLATE AND PRALINES LEVEL 1, SAVOUR CHOCOLATE AND PATISSERIE SCHOOL, MELBOURNE (AU)** 

FEB. 2016 - JULY 2016

**CERITIFICATE: PASTRY AND BAKING BASIC TECHNIQUES, FOOD GENIOUS**ACADEMY, MILAN (ITALY)

2009 - 2015

**DIPLOMA: MARKETING AND FOREIGNERS LANGUAGES,** IIS GADDA ROSSELLI, GALLARATE (ITALY)

# **LANGUAGES**

**ITALIAN: MOTHER TONGUE** 

**ENGLISH:** FLUENTLY **SPANISH:** FLUENTLY

**FRENCH: BASIC**